MOHAMMAD SAEID MOHEBBI

Senior Full Stack Developer

+989135034803 @ msmohebbi76@gmail.com @msmcode.ir Plran, Kerman

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with 4+ years' experience in Web & Back-end development using Django and 3+ years' experience in cross-platform development using Flutter, I enjoy learning new techs to solve people's problems and create incredible products and make it a better world with the help of technology.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

09/2023 - Present

Vibogram

Canada, Vancouver

Global social media platform with market place, job seeker and dating. Explore new friends, make connections, chat with them and have a good time.

Android & IOS app base on Flutter & Django & Azure cloud.

- Designed and deployed a comprehensive backend system on Azure Cloud.
- Implemented a real-time chat messaging system that supports audio and video calls.
- Developed an algorithm capable of identifying similar or nearby friends.
- Constructed a global marketplace equipped with an intelligent recommendation system.

Google Play - App Store

Full Stack Developer

05/2023 - 10/2023

Daric Canada, Toronto

Online currency exchange.

Send money to others, or receive money from others.

Android & IOS app base on Flutter & Firebase.

- Collaborated with real-time data and instant transactions.
- Implemented currency rate updates and adjustments based on reliable APIs.
- Constructed a secure management panel with varying access permissions.

Google Play - App Store

Full Stack Developer

06/2023 - 12/2023

Novin Taxi Iran, Karaj

Intercity transportation service for travelers.

Integrated applications for both users & drivers

Android, IOS & Web app base on Flutter, Django & PostgreSQL.

- Designed a optimum navigation system based on traffic data.
- Implemented a dedicated algorithm to identify suitable driver for each trip.
- Enhanced user communication through an advanced notification system.
- https://novintaxi.com Bazaar SibApp



SKILLS

Dart & Flutter • Python •

Django & Django Rest Framework •

HTML & CSS • NGINX • Docker •

GIT • CI/CD • Firebase • Azure •

PostgreSQL • MySQL • MongoDB

EDUCATION

Pharmacy Doctorate

Kerman University of Medical Science 09/2016 - 01/2023

LANGUAGES

English

Proficient



FIND ME ONLINE

Full Resume https://msmcode.ir

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/msmoh ebbi76

GitHub

https://github.com/msmohebbi

CTO 08/2022 – 06/2024

Unidooni Iran, Kerman

Complete guide for international students to find study plans and courses

Over 50,000 studies, courses and universities around the world.

Android, IOS & Web app base on Flutter, Django & PostgreSQL.

- Built by 40,000+ cleanly-architected lines of code.
- · Worked with big data and optimized various database queries.
- · Open Al assist deploy for writing blog contents.
- https://unidooni.com Bazaar SibApp

Full Stack Developer

09/2021 - 01/2022

Shakib Learn

Iran, Kerman

E-learning platform around medical and veterinary topics.

Android, IOS & Web app base on Flutter, Django & MySQL.

- Design, develop and deploy Android, IOS and Web apps from scratch.
- Increased company revenue by 130% within the first six months by switching the WordPress website to an Android, iOS and web app.



Full Stack Developer

02/2022 - 05/2022

Secret TV Iran, Kerman

Movie app with social media about motivation, soul, body and mind. Android, IOS & Web app base on Flutter, Django & PostgreSQL.

- Design, develop and deploy Android, IOS and Web apps from scratch.
- Increased the number of users by 200% by designing & developing user-friendly social media for communicating users.
- https://secret-tv.com Google Play SibApp

CEO 07/2021 – 03/2022

Delif Iran, Kerman

Online delivery and marketplace app & Web app.

Built in 3 applications for users, drivers & seller.

Android, IOS & Web app base on Flutter, Django & PostgreSQL.

- Design, develop and deploy Android, IOS and Web apps from scratch.
- Received 1 billion Iranian Rial investment from KermanSTP.

https://delif.ir

Full Stack Developer

03/2020 - 03/2021

DGAP Iran, Tehran

Online shop for full-electric barber chairs.

Built in 2 websites for user & CRM,

Web site base on Django, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap & MySQL.

- Develop CRM for sending SMS and track clients requests, calls and payments.
- Design introduction page for products and purchase conditions.

https://dgapco.ir

REFRENCES

Ali Pezeshki from Daric and Vibogram

alipilot149@gmail.com +1 604 250 4757

Mohammad Hossein Jahanshahi from Unidooni

mhjhays@gmail.com +989133407236

Mohammad Moosavi from Secret TV

secret.tv.live@gmail.com +989131433262

Hossein Shakib from ShakibLearn

hosseinshakib97@gmail.com +989135896354

Mohammad Amin Fakhr Abadi from Delif

amin.fakhrabadi.2018@gmail.com +989215969959

Meysam Barfe from DGAP m barfe@yahoo.com

m_barfe@yahoo.coi +989131922701